Center for Traditional Music and Dance collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Event documentation, 1968-2015
  - Events, 2007
    - Vechornytsi, 2007-2011
      - Moving Images, ca. 2007-2011
        - 2 video files (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07/10; Note on media: Ukranian Vechornytsi Village Dance Party
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07/10; Note on media: Vechornytsi Dance Program
        - 3 video files (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07/10; Note on media: Vechornytsi Manhattan
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07/11; Note on media: NY Bandura Ensemble
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07/11; Note on media: Soldiers' Songs
    - Sizhu Concert Series, March-May 2007
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2007
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: Sizhu - Rubin Museum (Box-folder 10/22)
      - Moving Images, 2007-03-25
        - 1 video disc (DVD), CCI 07-0325 DVD; Note on media: Music from China (Box 19)
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI_07-0325-DVD
      - Moving Images, 2007-04-29
        - 1 video disc (DVD), CCI 07-0429 DVD; Note on media: Melody of Dragon (Box 19)
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI_07-0429-DVD
      - Moving Images, 2007-05-12
        - 1 video disc (DVD), CCI 07-0512 DVD; Note on media: Min Xiao Fen (Box 19)
    - Vechornytsi, April 2007
      - Moving Images, 2007-04-21
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 07-0421_vr1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 07-0421_vr2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 07-0421_vr3
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 07-0421_vr3a
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-0421_1; Note on media: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-0421_2; Note on media: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-0421_1-VR3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-0421_1a
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-0421_2b
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-0421_3a
    - Ukrainian Modernism, April 2007
      - Moving Images, 2007-04-28
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 07-0428_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 07-0428_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 07-0428_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 07-0428_2
    - Saints and Sinners: Songs of Worship, Penitence, and Celebration, May 2007
      - Moving Images, 2007-05-17
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-0517_1; Note on media: New York Bandura Ensemble, camera 1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-0517_2; Note on media: New York Bandura Ensemble, camera 1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-0517_3; Note on media: Ukrainian Museum
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-0517_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-0517_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-0517_3
    - Vechornytsi, June 2007
      - Moving Images, 2007-06-30
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-0630_1; Note on media: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-0630_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-0630_3
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-0630_4
    - Lincoln Center Out of Doors: Heritage Sunday, August 2007
      - Moving Images, 2007-08-12
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: LCOOD 07-0812_1; Note on media: The Power of Music: Songs of Love and Struggle
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: LCOOD 07-0812_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: LCOOD 07-0813_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: LCOOD 07-0813_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., LCOOD 07-0813_1; Note on media: Super Manden
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., LCOOD 07-0813_2; Note on media: Super Manden
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., LCOOD 07-0813_1; Note on media: Viento de Agua
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., LCOOD 07-0813_2; Note on media: Viento de Agua
    - New York World Festival: Music Around the Mediterranean, September 2007
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2007-09-16
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: Linn Cary Mehta Brunch - NYWF (Box-folder 10/29)
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: Music Around the Mediterranean (Box-folder 10/30)
      - Sound Recordings, 2007-09-16
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 07-0916.1a; Note on media: Dimonis d'Albopas/Orchestra de Tangier/Christos Tiktapanidis (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 07-0916.1b.2a; Note on media: Christos Tiktapanidis/Amalia Christodoulakis Papastefanou/Hassan Hakmoun (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), NYWF 07-0916.2b; Note on media: Hassan Hakmoun (Box 17)
        - 9 audio files (wav): digital., NYWF_07_0916_1a; Note on media: Central Park Summer Stage
        - 8 audio files (wav): digital., NYWF_07_0916_1b_2a
        - 3 audio files (wav): digital., NYWF_07_0916_2b
    - Sounds of the Prairies: Music and Dance of the Ukrainian Settlers of Western Canada, October 2007
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2007-10-20
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 10/33)
      - Moving Images, 2007-10-16 to 2007-10-22
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-1016_1; Note on media: with Brian Cherwick (tsymbalist--hammered dulcimer player--and scholar)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-1016_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-1016_3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-1016_1; Note on media: Brian Cherwick Workshop
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-1016_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-1016_3
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-1019_1; Note on media: featuring Brian Cherwick (tsymbaly player/ethnomusicologist)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-1019_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-1019_1; Note on media: Brian Cherwick and Friends
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-1019_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-1020_1; Note on media: Led by Brian Cherwick (tsymbaly player/ethnomusicologist) and Andriy Nahachewsky (folk dance scholar/dance master)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-1020_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-1020_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-1022_1; Note on media: lecture/presentation on Canadian-Ukrainian prairie music
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-1022_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 07-1022_2
    - Yiddish Dance Research Symposium, December 2007
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2007-12-09
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 10/34)
      - Sound Recordings, 2007-12-09 to 2007-12-10
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_3
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_5
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_5a
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_6
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_7
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_8
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_9
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_10
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_11
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_12
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_13
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1209_14
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_5
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_6
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_7
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_8
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_9
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_10
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_11
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_12
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_13
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209_14
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1209
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1210_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: YDRS 07-1210_2; Note on media: Michael Winegrad
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1210_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1210_1a
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., YDRS 07-1210_2; Note on media: Michael Winegrad
    - Other events, 2007
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 2007, Note on folder: Pachamama Peruvian Arts (Box-folder 10/21)
        - 1 folder, 2007, Note on folder: Ukranian Museum - Musical Reflections (Box-folder 10/23)
        - 1 folder, 2007-01-19, Note on folder: Weekend of World Music - Rubin Museum (Box-folder 10/25)
        - 1 folder, 2007-01-20, Note on folder: Touring Artist Flier - ADAP (Box-folder 10/26)
        - 1 folder, 2007-02-25, Note on folder: Spring Concert - East West Music (Box-folder 10/27)
        - 1 folder, 2007-09-09, Note on folder: Bandura Downtown (Box-folder 10/28)
        - 1 folder, 2007-09-26, Note on folder: Voices and Images from Bulgaria 1966 (Box-folder 10/31)
        - 1 folder, 2007-09-28, Note on folder: Pachamama Peruvian Arts (Box-folder 10/32)
      - Moving Images
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2007-02-25, AFC 2014/044: CCCI 07-0225_01; Note on media: possibly Wossing Center, student recital
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2007-09-29, AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-0929_1; Note on media: Vechornytsi series: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2007-09-29, AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-0929_2; Note on media: Vechornytsi series: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2007-11-01, AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 07-1101_2; Note on media: Joe cam 1, tape #2; show and interview
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2007-11-09, AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 07-1109_1; Note on media: Armistice Day Concert featuring Ukranian songs and poetry reflecting on the First World War
  - Events, 2008
    - Chinese Music Recital, January 2008
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2008-01-06
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 10/39)
      - Moving Images, 2008-01-06
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 08-0106_01
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 08-0106_01; Note on media: Chinese Youth Recital
    - A Ukrainian Christmas and New Year's Concert with Cheres and Friends, January 2008
      - Moving Images, 2008-01-11
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0111_1; Note on media: Ukrainian Museum
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0111_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-0111_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-0111_2
    - Latin Fiesta!: Music and Dance of the Americas, January 2008
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2008-01-13
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 10/40)
      - Moving Images, 2008-01-13
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: TA 08-0113_1; Note on media: Teatro Heckscher of El Museo del Barrio
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: TA 08-0113_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., TA 08-0113_1; Note on media: Touring Artists Latin Fiesta!
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., TA 08-0113_2
    - Vechornytsi, Ukrainian Wave Community Cultural Initiative, March 2008
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2008
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 10/38)
      - Moving Images, 2008-03-01
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0301_1; Note on media: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0301_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0301_3
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0301_1; Note on media: Ukrainian East Village Restaurant
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0301_2
    - Ukrainian Women's Voices, May 2008
      - Moving Images, 2008-05-03
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 82 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0503_1; Note on media: Mariana Sadowska and friends
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-0503_1; Note on media: Ukrainian Women's Voices
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-0503_v1
    - Mapping Ukraine in Song, May 2008
      - Moving Images, 2008-05-09
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0509_1; Note on media: Ukrainian Museum
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0509_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-0509_1; Note on media: Border Ballads- Mapping Ukraine in song
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-0509_2
    - Vechornytsi, Ukrainian Wave Community Cultural Initiative, June 2008
      - Moving Images, 2008-06-14
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0614_1; Note on media: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0614_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0614_3
    - Love Songs and Dances from Cossack Ukraine, June 2008
      - Moving Images, 2008-06-19
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0619_1; Note on media: Julian Kytasty and the New York Bandura Ensemble
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-0619_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-0619_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-0619_2
    - Palomitay (Little Dove), Pachamama Peruvian Arts Student Presentation, June 2008
      - Moving Images, 2008-06-20
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 08-0620_1; Note on media: featuring students performing with faculty
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CCI 08-0620_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 08-0620_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CCI 08-0620_2
    - Songs of Truth: The Art of the Kobzari, November 2008
      - Moving Images, 2008-11-14
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-1114_1; Note on media: Julian Kytasty (bandurist/singer)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-1114_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-1114_1; Note on media: Songs of Truth Concert
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-1114_2
    - Vechornytsi,Carpathian Dance Party, November 2008
      - Moving Images, 2008-11-28
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-1128_1; Note on media: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-1128_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-1128_1; Note on media: Brooklyn Vechornytsi
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-1128_1; Note on media: Ukrainian Vechornytsi Carpathian Dance Party
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-1128_2
    - Vechornytsi, Ukrainian Wave Community Cultural Initiative, December 2008
      - Moving Images, 2008-12-14
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-1214_1; Note on media: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-1214_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 08-1214_1; Note on media: St. George Christmas recital
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-1214_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 08-1214_2
    - Other events, 2008
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 2008, Note on folder: Pachamama Peruvian Arts (Box-folder 10/35)
        - 1 folder, 2008, Note on folder: Sue Yeon Park - Touring Promo Card (Box-folder 10/36)
        - 1 folder, 2008, Note on folder: Ukrainian Museum (Box-folder 10/37)
        - 1 folder, 2008-06-05, Note on folder: Fourtieth Anniversary Benefit Dinner (Box-folder 10/41)
        - 1 folder, 2008-08-17, Note on folder: Heritage Sunday (Box-folder 10/42)
        - 1 folder, 2008-12-16, Note on folder: Beyond Boundaries: Klezmer Music in the Twenty-first Century (Box-folder 10/43)
        - 1 folder, 2008-2009, Note on folder: Touring Artists Roster (Box-folder 10/44)
      - Moving Images
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2008-01-06, AFC 2014/044: YDRS 08-0106; Note on media: Yiddish Dance Research Symposium
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2008-05-11, AFC 2014/044: YDRS 08-0511; Note on media: Yiddish Dance Research Symposium
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2008-05-24, AFC 2014/044: CCI 08-0524; Note on media: Afro-Peruvian percussion: Marcos Napa lesson with Anthony Apestegui
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., 2008-05-24, CCI 08-0524; Note on media: Afro-Peruvian Percussion
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2008-06-17, AFC 2014/044: 08-0617_1; Note on media: Pablo Mayor Trio
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2008-06-17, AFC 2014/044: 08-0617_2; Note on media: Pablo Mayor Trio
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2008-06-21, AFC 2014/044: CCI 08-0621; Note on media: NYSCA apprenticeship: Afro-Peruvian percussion: Marcos Napa teaching Anthony Apestegui
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., 2008-06-21, CCI 08-0621; Note on media: NYSCA apprenticeship: Marcos Napa Teaching Anthony Apestegui
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2008-08-14, AFC 2014/044: CCI 08-0814_01; Note on media: Interview towards NTSCA Folk Arts apprenticeship grant
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., 2008-08-14, CCI 08-0814_01; Note on media: Interview Towards NYSCA Folk Arts Apprenticeship Grant
  - Events, 2009
    - Tantshoyz, March 2009
      - Moving Images, 2009-03-15
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 09-0315_1; Note on media: Yiddish dance in Brooklyn, with dance leader Deborah Strauss and live klezmer band
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 09-0315_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 09-0315_3
      - Moving Images, 2009-05-11
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 09-0511_1; Note on media: Yiddish dance, Workmen's Circle
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 09-0511_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 09-0511_3
      - Moving Images, 2009-09-03
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 09-0903_1; Note on media: Tantshoyz: Yiddish dance, Workmen's Circle
      - Moving Images, 2009-12-03
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 09-1203_1; Note on media: Yiddish dance, Workmen's Circle
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 09-1203_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 09-1203_3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., ANSKYCCI 09-1203_3a
      - Moving Images, ca. 2009-2011
        - 16 video files (mp4): digital., ANSKYCCI 09/11; Note on media: Tantshoyz
    - New York Chinese Youth Ensemble Concert, March 2009
      - Moving Images, 2009-03-21
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CHINCCI 09-0321_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CHINCCI 09-0321_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV), AFC 2014/044: CHINCCI 09-0321_1_showcase; Note on media: showcase of young Chinese musicians, Hamilton-Madison Settlement House
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV), AFC 2014/044: CHINCCI 09-0321_2_showcase
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV), AFC 2014/044: CHINCCI 09-0321_3_showcase
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CHINCCI 09-0321_1a
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CHINCCI 09-0321_2a
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CHINCCI 09-0321_3
    - Julian Kytasty Concert, April 2009
      - Moving Images, 2009-04-03
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-0403_1; Note on media: Julian Kytasty playing the repertoire of Hryhory Kytasty
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-0403_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 09-0403_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., UKRCCI 09-0403_2
    - Ge Chang Hui: Chinese Song Swap, April 2009
      - Moving Images, 2009-04-05
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CHINCCI 09-0405_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CHINCCI 09-0405_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CHINCCI 09-0405_3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CHINCCI 09-0405_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CHINCCI 09-0405_2
    - Vechornytsi, Ukrainian Wave Community Cultural Initiative, April to November 2009
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2009
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Moving Images, 2009-04-25
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-0425_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-0425_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-0425_1; Note on media: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Cheres Folk Ensemble, music (led by Ukrainian Wave co-Artistic Director Andriy Milavsky)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-0425_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-0425_3
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-0425_4
      - Moving Images, 2009-09-26
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-0926_1; Note on media: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-0926_2; Note on media: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
      - Moving Images, 2009-11-21
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-1121_1; Note on media: Tamara Chernyakhovska (dance instructor); Andriy Milavsky and Cheres (music)
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-1121_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 09-1121_3
    - CTMD Benefit Dinner, June 2009
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2009-06-04
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: A Night in Istanbul Benefit Dinner (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Moving Images, 2009-06-04